A-Acrobatic Silky?
Ouch!
Takakura-sama, are you all right?
Ow.
What a lewd state you are in!
To expose yourself to me like that...
It must mean you're presuming
a betrothal already!
Very well!
You have powers as well?
I see, so that is why you were able
to enter our void space.
We will take your banana organs
while we're at it.
- Labor, labor...
- Hold on!
Let me put something on!
Takakura-sama, I will deal with them!
Full of defects, covered in mud,
that's fine, that's fine.
Yup, that's fine, that's fine, now...
Labor!
Serpoian Form Serpogrammetry!
Wait up!
Don't include me in your attack!
You're a cheap hire. There are
countless replacements for you.
What was that just now?
I feel like I crashed into an invisible wall.
Snap!
Chiquitita, you have a dream?
Shy my chotchiki for you.
Chiquitita, you wake from a dream?
This is...
Where are the clothes?
Jet Punch!
That's a respectable punch.
Thank you, deez!
But if it doesn't connect,
it's not much of anything.
Snap!
TAKAKURA
Serpoian Form Serpogrammetry!
Hold it! Stop that!
What a nuisance!
You seem to be in love with me.
Not one bit.
I'm sorry. I already have
someone in my heart.
But I'll give you as many chances
as you need to try to win my heart.
That is...
...the conditions of an attractive lady.
Argh! My head is stuck!
Now, I'll take the nuisance...
I have caught you, woman person.
What is this? It's going to crush me!
You just thought, "You can use psychic powers
even without saying Serpogrammetry," yes?
I don't care about any of that!
I didn't overlook the fact
that you dropped your guard.
I don't care about that!
Just let me out of this!
But this is quite interesting.
There are multiple persons with special powers
in the same location.
There is hope for us
to seek further evolution.
Your movements are remarkable...
...but you are not all too powerful.
This wasn't in the plans, but we will take
your banana organs as well while we're at it.
I am the chosen one!
I won't lose to the likes of you!
The light of hope will come
from the heavens and—
Chiquitita.
That's right. You have been chosen.
Chosen for our evolution.
Now, let's begin.
Hold on just a second!
You were after me, weren't you?
I'll take you on right now!
Takakura-sama! You're still...
There are things that are
more important than clothes!
Man, I hate this. I wanna go home...
That's right, that's right.
We want your banana organs.
However...
We can do both of you simultaneously.
As long as there are three of us.
This is...
The transformation is wearing off.
This is possible when the three of us
combine our psychokinesis.
The Awesome Zone.
Inside this area...
...all transformations...
...let alone standing up...
...will be impossible.
- However...
- ...this...
- ...has...
- ...one...
...flaw.
We cannot enter there, either.
Thus...
We will have him beat you up
until you can no longer move.
Stop that! If you do that, he'll die!
Please, stop!
Impossible!
He broke through the Awesome Zone?
No, he didn't!
Our psychokinesis
is being repelled by someone!
Oh no! The woman person is here!
Momo-chan, I really missed you.
Okarun, you moron!
Don't you be making out with that bitch!
I'd never forget your damn faces!
EPISODE 9
MERGE!
SERPO DOVER DEMON NESSIE!
Momo-chan, I really missed you.
Shut up! Don't look at me, you perv!
Until we harvest
the man person's banana organ...
...we wanted the woman person
under confinement! That's what we told it!
What exactly is that thing doing?
It's annoying that Momo Ayase is rescuing me,
but I have no choice.
You shall lend us a hand!
Wait, is that Acro-Silky?
I'll help you out, but I won't let you
have Ken Takakura-sama!
Miss Ayase!
Come on, Momo Ayase!
What are you doing?
You have to hold them back
with your magic!
I don't know how,
but we have the advantage!
Let's wake up the Gig Worker now!
Damn it! Do your job properly
or we'll lower your pay!
Sorry, this is a bit impossible.
You're such a bother!
No! Anything but that!
Stop!
Yellow and black
is the mark of courage.
Are you able to fight 24 hours?
Regain, Regain, our own Regain.
The mark of courage on our briefcases.
Can you fight far off in a distant world?
Business Man!
Japanese Business Man!
That's right!
Take them...
...and beat them up...
...so they can't move anymore!
Man, you irritate me.
You mention that name, you die.
So powerful!
Our psychic powers are being pushed back!
Gig Worker! Go after that woman person!
I won't let you.
You're not going to ignore me.
Makes me wilt.
If we don't have that
psychic thing going, it's all ours!
Salary...
Uppercut!
I can't see the attack!
That thing is bad news!
Mantis!
He dodged!
I can see this thing's punches.
Mantis!
You said that I am lacking in power,
didn't you?
Then...
I'll simply nail
your weak spot multiple times.
I am one with Takakura-sama!
Hey! You guys are way too close!
You guys will both get blown away!
Oh my, are you jealous?
As if!
Momo-chan, that's great advice.
I am an awkward fellow after all.
Do you guys wanna die?
I'm sorry, Miss Ayase!
Come on, get a grip already!
You're the one in charge of holding back
their weird powers!
Sheesh, you are so useless.
Your pay will be cut by 60 percent.
N-No way.
What was that just now?
Water!
My feet don't touch the bottom!
What's going on here?
The wall and ceiling is all water now!
Crap.
It's here.
Crap, crap, crap!
We're gonna escape for now!
Hold on! Why are you calling the shots?
I'm the leader here!
It's Nessie!
Takakura-kun is getting excited.
He's so cute.
Damn you guys!
No, we're in Kamigoe City,
so should I call it Kamissie?
Oh, fine! Then you guys can get
real chummy and stare at Nessie!
I'm outta here!
Oh, so that thing is called Nessie?
Takakura-kun, you know so much.
Come on! What have you been doing?
You weren't able to hold back
the woman person at all!
You're also getting a 60 percent pay cu...
How could you?
Nessie is really bad news!
- Why are you attacking us?
- That's what I've been saying!
You're supposed to get
that woman person over there!
Hey! Takakura-kun, wait...
Miss Shiratori!
That was from him?
Business Punch!
Does he punch harder underwater?
Is he a Mantisian that has
the characteristics of a mantis shrimp?
Mantis! Mantis!
Yours truly can exert
real power underwater!
The underwater punching power
of yours truly is ten times that on land.
Huh?
Ten times!
Still need air, huh?
Get him!
You should be able to swim at pretty high speed
with Turbo Granny's leg strength!
Makes me wilt.
I'm gonna die!
I can't swim!
Turbo Granny can't swim!
Huh?
This is the worst situation ever!
How are we supposed to fight like this?
I don't know the answer either!
We're in trouble if we take too long!
If we don't hurry up and save
that stupid girl, she'll drown!
Miss Ayase, what about your psychic powers?
I can reach if we're right below her,
but that mantis shrimp guy
is in the way and I can't get close!
Then I'll draw that guy's attention,
so please grab Miss Shiratori
in the meantime!
What are you talking about?
If you just plunge in like that, you'll end up
exactly like that stupid girl!
Don't make things harder for me, okay?
You don't have to say it like that!
I'm just trying to make myself useful!
And it doesn't mean jack
if you cause even more trouble!
That's why I said we need to hurry up and run!
You guys are at fault
for making out all the time!
We weren't making out!
You've been making out!
This whole time!
You pinned her down on the ground
in the courtyard!
So it was bothering you!
No, it's not!
I don't care what some liar
is doing with some stupid girl!
Hold on a second!
If you actually care,
then tell me honestly that you do!
If it's weighing on your mind,
please let me explain myself!
I don't care how much other people
will take things the wrong way,
but I don't want you
to have the wrong idea, Miss Ayase!
I want you to have a proper understanding
of everything!
Don't touch me, pervert!
Oh, sorry.
How can you say that
when you look like that?
Miss Ayase!
I'm sorry!
That was beyond my control!
I won't touch you ever again!
That's a great idea!
Huh?
Okarun, stay still!
This is rough.
All right, let's try it.
Stop with your futile resistance!
What the hell is that?
I grab Okarun really hard,
and push him forward!
I propel him with my psychic powers
as if I'm catching a lively fish, and ride it!
You can't escape attacks from yours truly!
Get up there!
That's amazing!
Miss Ayase, you're such a genius!
I know that!
Hey, come on. Wake up!
She probably swallowed a lot of water.
Don't hate me for this, okay?
Forced resuscitation!
Miss Shiratori! I'm glad!
Is this a dream?
You dumbass!
We haven't resolved anything yet!
Take your clothes off! It's hard to move you
when there's water resistance.
Huh?
I've already decided I'm not stripping down
until my wedding night!
Strip!
It's not fair that you escaped upwards!
Oh, right now yours truly
has them cornered.
Give me a bit more time.
What?
Each and every one of you are useless!
His attack power is amazing, but he's so stupid
he assaults everything in sight.
Gig Worker has high attack power underwater,
but he takes too many breaths
and the enemy ends up escaping.
Sorry.
That's enough. This is a case
where we will all merge together.
We will use this Body Cable to become one.
YOU MUST ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY
AND RAISE AN ANIMAL FOR ITS ENTIRE LIFE!
You have to assume responsibility.
Takakura-kun, you saw me in lingerie.
I did not.
You in lingerie is only worth
one piece of candy.
Anyway, I need both of you
to get fired up!
We can't win unless we all use
everything we've got!
Sure.
Don't tell me what to do!
I'm the leader!
Here goes!
One, two...
What a shame. Ran out of water.
That was close!
What was that?
Is that even possible?
Miss Ayase, look at that!
It's pooling water into its neck!
So it can't shoot continuously!
Which means, if we break that thing's neck,
it can't shoot lasers anymore!
Let's do it!
Now might be our chance!
Let's get close and attack!
You just thought we only had
the high-compression water blast, didn't you?
We may look like this, but we are
a close-combat in-fighter UMA.
Oh no!
Hey, get a grip! Are you okay?
That hurt! I'm not okay!
Then you're fine!
That thing has the punching guy's arm!
When did they merge together?
We can't get close like that!
That damn Serpoian brought the punching guy
to cover for Nessie's weakness all along!
It's too strong! Laser beams
and mantis shrimp punches...
We might've had a chance on land,
but there's nothing we can do underwater!
Okarun, what'd you just say?
There's nothing we can do!
Not that one!
You said mantis shrimp punches?
Too bad.
The high-compression water blast
has run out yet again.
But we have endless ways to kill you.
You are a very dangerous person,
so we will kill you first then dissect you.
We can simply wait for you to drown
but we have used a bit too much time.
Can we punch you to death?
Wh-What?
What is going on here?
You shouldn't have merged together
with that Mantisian.
A mantis shrimp's punching powers
are unparalleled underwater.
But on land, it can never
unleash a punch at full strength.
Including him.
If he tried to go all-out,
he'd have ended up like you now.
He'd have imploded
from the impact of his own punch.
I can stay underwater like this
for hours on end!
But what about you?
Will you drown first? Or will you be severed
by the high-compression water blast first?
I can't swim.
But if there's a path to run...
I can go full throttle.
Hold on just a second!
We're back?
We defeated them?
The ground is hard.
This is the hallway!
Thank you, hallway.
Thank you for being so hard!
What's that about?
I dunno. It's hilarious.
Huh?
What are they doing?
These guys are buck naked and hugging!
Ayase from Class B
and that four-eyes is going at it!
No!
The prim Miss Shiratori
from Class D is naked, too!
Why is this happening?
Why are they all naked?
Nessie was simply too wicked!
Was it a surviving Plesiosaur?
But I never thought
it would merge with an alien.
The merger between an UMA and an alien
is like a dream for me!
Takakura-kun, you know so much.
EPISODE 10
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A CATTLE MUTILATION?
Next episode,
"Have You Ever Seen a Cattle Mutilation?"
Man, I was caught in a weird situation.
This really sucks!